Coolio man oh yeah
sly oh hey I got to go yeah Terry out
Terry how you doing man hey pretty good
Gabe oh got something on your
shirt not today
Terry looks like gab's come out to
play you do have something on your shirt
though no I don't yeah you kind of do
I'm pretty sure I don't got a clean
shirt at my desk if you want me to get
it for you don't see why that would be
necessary well because the shirt you
have on right now it's not clean except
for that it is me I have a clean shirt
you you have some Schmutz on your jamy
jam no there is no schuts on my jamy
jam you know what why don't I just get
it for you yeah why don't you do that
yeah and there we go did you get
[Laughter]
it I almost got you yeah was that close
almost I mean I'm thinking damn he
[Laughter]
good you know what the funny thing is
what's that now I guess from when I
dabbed your shirt with the paper towel
and I'm not playing the game right now
but I actually I must have got some
paper towel fuzz on your shirt
[Music]
so
hey so how long has Karen been wearing
her hair up like
[Music]
that
I want you have to go through that and I
I'm sorry I have it hey Terry what's
going
on uh nothing
morning yeah I'm having a terrific
morning great hope there's nothing on my
shirt cuz I can't look
down oh no dude we're not doing that
right now okay there nothing on your
shirt no one cares about your shirt
everything's not about
you I'm trying to have a conversation
with Karen right now
so
you okay Terry just pisses me
[Music]
off
I got it I got it there's no way you're
going to get no oh yeah yeah I do have
schuts there schuts all over me now he
can't deny that Terry's not going to
know what hit him I will win I
[Music]
win
o what what happened Terry
[Applause]
[Music]
died
be right
back hey
Cherry it's
Gabe I um just wanted to let you know
that
um that you didn't get me Terry you
didn't get me because on the day that
you died there was Schmutz on my shirt
so guess who wins the game Terry I do I
win you
[Music]
[Applause]
lose
Terry he flicked
me
[Music]
I but I don't
need